Jordan:
She runs an amazing restaurant
going global soon.
But also you are a very creative person.
Now, efficiency must be huge for you.
Mia:
Oh, absolutely.
Host:
But ok, KEY QUESTION…
What does the Galaxy Z Fold7 mean to you?
Jordan:
Welcome to this week’s episode,
“Should we Unfold?”
Where we ask, is now the time to actually switch?
Mia:
Oh, that’s a big question.
Jordan:
The Galaxy Z Fold has always been a favorite
among tech enthusiasts.
Could this be the model that truly captures
the attention of every smartphone user?
Jordan:
And to help us figure it out,
we've got someone who's actually living with it.
She runs an amazing restaurant everybody's buzzing about,
going global soon,
but importantly, she recently switched to a foldable.
The Galaxy Z Fold7.
Jordan:
Mia, welcome!
Mia:
Hey, what's up? I'm very excited to be here.
Thank you for having me.
Jordan:
Yeah, absolutely. Thank you for joining us.
Okay. So, word on the street,
is that you have the new Z Fold7.
Mia:
Yes, I do.
Jordan:
My first impression of foldable was
cool idea, but a bit bulky.
What was your first take?
Mia:
Honestly, me too.
But then I got my hands on the Z Fold7,
and it really surprised me just how slim it is.
Jordan:
From what I’ve heard,
they’ve reimagined the design from scratch.
With a slimmer hinge,
a thinner display,
and more efficient internal layering,
the device is noticeably sleeker
– without compromising durability.
Jordan:
But okay, key question.
If it’s like a regular phone folded,
why bother unfolding? Like what's the plus?
Mia:
Right. That’s the thing. It's like your regular phone.
You can still do a quick text, all that.
But then, it's got this really nice extra feature,
right, extra gear,
that when you open it…
Jordan:
Kinda like a mini tablet.
Mia:
Exactly, yes.
And it’s perfect for gaming, too.
Jordan:
You know where my brain goes next,
is what about the battery life?
Cause that's got such a big screen.
Does that not just die instantly?
Mia:
I thought that too, but honestly,
the battery life has been really impressive.
Even when I watch videos from day to night,
they somehow managed to keep it slim
and gave it a more efficient battery.
Jordan:
So there was no compromise?
Mia:
I haven't noticed one.
Jordan:
Now, efficiency must be huge for you.
Mia:
Oh, absolutely. Non-stop.
Jordan:
You’re opening a new restaurant space.
Mia:
Mhmm.
Jordan:
How has the Z Fold7
helped with the practical side of your daily life?
Mia:
The start of the day is a good example.
This is my Now Brief.
And it’s like my personal dashboard.
This gives me the key info for the day.
Jordan:
It’s kinda like a personal assistant.
Mia:
Exactly, yes.
And another big practical thing recently
was working on the interior in our new place in Thailand.
Mia:
Hi Gemini.
This is my restaurant.
I want to add a local vibe to my interior.
Gemini:
Of course!
So, you might consider incorporating elements
like rich, colorful fabrics
like table runners, traditional Thai artwork,
or wooden carvings.
Mia:
These look interesting.
Which one would you recommend
among these two table runners?
Gemini: Given the light and airy feel of your restaurant,
the table runners on the left would be a great choice.
It has a delicate pattern and lighter color.
Jordan:
It’s very practical. It makes sense.
But also, you're a very creative person.
How does the phone, especially
the camera, feed into the creative side?
Mia:
Well, having 200 megapixels definitely helps.
Jordan:
Same level as the S25 Ultra.
Mia:
Yeah, yeah.
Like, we were on a vacation recently.
My husband and daughter were playing.
I snapped a picture,
didn't think much of it.
But when I zoomed in,
that image sparked an idea for a dish.
The light, the detail with such clarity.
And it’s not just in bright light either.
Mia:
Low light is where it really shines.
Once a month, just a casual dinner,
very low warm light,
and one night, it suddenly started
pouring rain outside.
It wasn't all grainy or dark,
you can really see them clearly,
captured the whole moment.
And then afterwards,
I can do a quick edit
right there on the unfolded screen.
And even make the sounds I want clearer.
Friend:
Oh my god!
Jordan:
That's amazing.
Mia:
Cute.
Look?
Jordan:
That’s almost perfect.
Mia:
Almost is never good enough for me.
No. No. No. But I'm gonna take out the microphone
that's like right in your face.
How about now?
Jordan:
Wow, I hate to say this about my own photo.
That’s perfect.
Mia:
I told you.
Jordan:
Okay. Wow. This has been really eye opening.
Like, I came into this with so many questions,
and now I'm leaving actually considering it.
Mia:
Look, I'm not trying to convince anyone,
but if the tech actually helps you live
and create better, it's worth looking at.
Jordan:
Absolutely.
Mia:
Right?
Jordan:
Alright. Well, thank you so much for sharing
this with all of us.
Mia:
Oh, thank you for having me.
Jordan:
Of course. And for those of you tuning in,
thank you again.
We'll catch you next week.