This is Zoe.
Junior project manager by day,
And a budding tech influencer by night.
But she’s not in it alone.
Introducing Galaxy Tab S11 Ultra
The thinnest and most powerful Galaxy Tab ever.
Zoe’s subscriber count? A little less impressive.
Perhaps she found a shortcut?
Hey Gemini. Looking at my channel stats,
what direction should I go in with my next video?
It looks like your videos about tech that
“doesn’t need to be complicated” are performing well.
So appeal to a non tech-savvy audience?
Exactly. Your audience seems to
really connect with straightforward tech tips.
Equipped with this new insight,
Zoe got to work on her script.
Atrial fibrillation...
slee—--eewww
Ah!
Ah! Looks like somebody wanted to help out a little!
No worries, Olive.
Zoe already has a little “assistance.”
See?
Just go with it.
Yeees,
post it!
And before you knew it, Zoe gained more..
..…a FEW
more followers.
Hey, we all gotta start somewhere.
Now, after leveling up her writing,
she focused on her drawing.
And she was not afraid to experiment with her creativity.
With the new-found power at her
fingertips
Her artistic range quickly expanded and improved
In detail
and expression
Because her thumbnails went from amateur…
to amazing.
Ummm…Muah!
Even in work mode,
she effortlessly switched from one task to another…
and another
….aaaaaand
another
Her productivity truly went through the roof.
Hmm..
is something bothering her?
How can I improve this background for my tech reviews?
Let’s start with the bookshelf -
try removing some of the smaller items to declutter it.
What about lighting?
You want to make sure you’re well-lit.
Now she had the perfect set-up.
On camera, at least.
It was the set-up for success!
It was like all of her talent had finally been brought to life..
Zoe continued to check off things to do
And with each one, her following grew
She stepped up her game
Even editing footage like a pro
With powerful performance and speed fueling her every task
And after successfully completing many to-do’s
She turned them into TA-DAs
in no time.
Zoe finally realized that all she had needed to unlock her potential
Was her Galaxy Tab S11 Ultra.