Hi, I'm Lara Jade a New York-based fashion and beauty photographer.
Hello, I’m Jay Lim,
a fashion photographer.
For this project,
I shot with the Galaxy S25 Edge
at Seoul Fashion Week, Korea’s biggest fashion event.
Using the Galaxy S25 Edge as my primary creative tool in this setting
allowed me to capture that atmosphere in detail.
My first thought was, wow,
I didn’t expect a phone to be this slim.
The S25 Edge allowed me to shoot with
total confidence and freedom.
In fashion photography,
you’ve got to capture every fabric texture
and accessory detail.
The S25 Edge’s 200MP camera brought all of that out so clearly.
The S25 Edge reminded me of how I work with my 24-70mm lens
because it offers a similar flexibility and speed.
Having control over
ISO and shutter speed myself,
that was the part I really loved.
I used to spend so much time thinking and time spent in front of the computer editing.
Now it feels like a thing of the past.
Streamlined.
The S25 Edge is not only a sleek device,
it streamlines the entire creative process.
And something a lot of photographers I think would be excited to use.